<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OFFERSHUB BUSINESS</string>

    <string name="nav_open">Open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="oops_no_item_found">Oups !! No item found</string>

    <string name="reload">Reload</string>
    <string name="choose_image_from">Choose Image from</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>>
    <string name="camera">Camera</string>

    <string name="share_content">Discover amazing deals and exclusive offers with offersHub!  Your go-to app for the best discounts on everything you love. Download it now and start saving big! %s</string>

    <string name="please_wait">Please Wait</string>

    <array name="category">
        <item>Fashion</item>
        <item>Jewellery</item>
        <item>Pharmacy</item>
        <item>Furniture</item>
    </array>

    <array name="offer_type">
        <item>Plain Offer</item>
        <item>Discount Price</item>
        <item>Flat Percentage</item>
    </array>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>

    <string name="about_us" translatable="false">       Thank you for being a part of the <b><font color="red">"OFFERSHUB"</font></b> family. Our mission at <b><font color="red">"OFFERSHUB"</font></b> is to help users discover nearby offers and discounts while supporting local retail businesses in boosting their sales.\n\n Crafted with care in Pondicherry, <b><font color="red">"OFFERSHUB"</font></b> serves as a platform for local retail businesses to advertise their offerings effectively, at no cost or minimal expense.\n\n While we currently do not provide delivery services, we are excited to announce that doorstep delivery will soon be available.\n\n<font color="red">Key Features:</font></string>
    <string name="test_bullet">
        <ul>
            <li><b>Advertisement Assistance:</b> Helps shops advertise their products and services.\n</li>
            <li><b>Lead Generation and Sales Boost:</b> Generates leads and boosts sales for local businesses.\n</li>
            <li><b>Free Registration:</b> No hidden charges, registration is entirely free.\n</li>
            <li><b>Localized Attention:</b> Attracts nearby customers to your shop.\n</li>
            <li><b>Cost-Effective Advertising:</b> Offers advertising at a very low price compared to other platforms.\n</li>
            <li><b>Multiple Shops, Single App:</b> Access multiple shops within one convenient application.\n</li>
            <li><b>Individual Shop Dashboard:</b> Provides each shop with its own dedicated dashboard.\n</li>
            <li><b>Comprehensive Insights:</b> Offers detailed insights and much more.</li>
        </ul>
    </string>

    <!--message notification channel info-->
    <string name="message_channel_name">MessageChannel</string>
    <string name="message_channel_description">This channel will take care of incoming chats</string>
</resources>